CARLOS DELGADO

Informatics Engineer / Frontend Developer https://delgadociteriowa.github.io/main/

About Me

Informatics Engineer with more than **five years** of experience, software development passionate (particularly for frontend web development). I consider myself to be a pro-active person who constantly pays attention to details. Right now I am interested in **ReactJs and Angular** development, however, open to other job positions as well.

Experience

Advoqt, Boston: Front-end Developer. 08/2019 - 12/2019.

- Cyber-security web-app development with Angular.
- UI/UX design and implementation for a login system.
- UI/UX design and implementation for a dashboard.

WBI, Caracas: Front-end Developer. 05/2017 - 06/2018.

- UI/UX implementation for the **International Telecommunications Satellite Organization** website.
- Web maintennance for Charlotte (USA) assurance company websites (WordPress).
- Development with Angular.

Jumperr, Caracas: Web Developer. 06/2018 - 10/2018.

- Web development for small businesses in Italy.
- UI/UX implementation.
- Wireframing and project planning.

El Universal, Caracas: UI/UX Specialist. 01/2016 - 03/2017.

- UI/UX implementation for baseball seasons score tables.
- Several widgets development in order to enrich user interactions.
- Maintenance for the four El Universal related websites.

Projects

SISKU: A web-app for creating and taking quizzes. This app features a whole CRUD system. **Link**: https://delgadociteriowa.github.io/sisku/

More: https://www.behance.net/delgadvociterio

Movie Reviews: A React application for reviewing movies. **Link**: https://github.com/delgadociteriowa/movie-reviews

React Learning Blog:

https://delgadociteriowa.medium.com/

Educational Background

Informatics Engineering Bachelor's Degree: Universidad Alejandro de Humboldt, Caracas. 01/2009 - 07/2014.

React Front to Back: Udemy (Brad Traversy). 09/2020.

Adobe Photoshop CC: Arts - Centro de Computación Gráfica. 10/2016.

Angular Front to Back: Udemy (Brad Traversy). 05/2020.

More: https://www.linkedin.com/in/delgadociterio/

Skills

Technical Skills: JavaScript - React - Redux - Angular - C# - Microsoft .NET - Git Version-control System - HTML - CSS - SASS UI/UX - Photoshop CC - Inkscape - JSON - Linux - Wireframes Development - Web Design - Project Planing.

Languages: Spanish (Native) - English: (Advanced)

Other Skills: Digital Drawing - Guitar.